Seen, it's Tubai Factory!
Our new album will be released on February 21, 2024!
The title is Third Moment.
The album will include all the singles we have performed since Yumi Kasai, Ori Egishi, Mari Fukuda, and Uchi Yofu joined the group, as well as songs we have performed only at our live shows, plus a few new songs.
Takuya Nakajima and SHOCK-EYE of Shonan no Kaze also contributed songs.
Thank you very much.
This is the third song that SHOCK-EYE has contributed, following Happy Cracker and Boys' Eyeism.
We have also done a recording, and that song is really nice.
The key sound is amazing.
There are many different songs, but I get the feeling that there will be not one but several songs that everyone can call and respond to.
I'm really looking forward to that.
Among the 4 wonderfully recorded songs, there are songs that have never been on Tsubaki Factory before, and there are songs that are very Tsubaki-esque, so I think you will really enjoy even the 4 songs.
Please get it.
The Limited First Edition comes with a variety of special features.
First of all, the Limited First Edition A includes all music videos of songs released after Tears for Heroine, Rattlesnake Diamonds, and Yakusoku Konnichiwa Kinenhi, as well as previously unreleased music videos that were not included on the bonus Blu-ray of the singles.
Amazing.
And to introduce you to it, there are many, many more, including a close-up version of the troubled nakirui kobangeki close-up version, and an evergreen version of Weakness Not Weakness Yoko Ewa.
And the Limited First Edition B comes with a video of the live performance of Tsubaki Factory's Summer Festival 2023 Shakunetsu held this summer.
This year's Shakunetsu was a new challenge for me, and I played the Japanese drums.
I was really nervous, but I was also quite surprised by my fans, so I hope you can enjoy watching us in various ways.
Tsubaki Factory's new album 3rd Moment will be released on February 21, 2024. Please listen to it.
And I have one more announcement.
On March 10, 2024, Tsubaki Factory will be holding a live concert to celebrate the 7th anniversary of their major debut.
We are able to hold the 7th anniversary live thanks to all of you who support us everyday.
The venue is Ichikawa City Cultural Hall. We hope to create memories of our 7th anniversary with you all.
We look forward to seeing you there.
This is Tsubaki Factory.
Thank you for watching.
Hello! This time we have Shizo Tanaka of Angulum and Nanami Kubota of Ocha no Ma!
Please stay with us until the end of the show.
Please bear with us until the end!
Six years ago around this time, we joined the Halo! Pro trainees around this time six years ago.
I think that if I were to describe our relationship, it's not as if we're friends or rivals in a professional relationship.
We are good friends, and even though I'm older than her, I don't feel that we are close enough to be friends.
I think we have a lot of fun when we talk.
Thank you very much.
I, Kubota, am also a friend.
Friends or sisters?
Sisters?
Sisters.
Twin sisters.
Sisters of about the same age.
Maybe there was a little rivalry when we were trainees.
That's true.
Now that I'm in a different group, I really don't feel like a rival.
I really feel like they are my friends and I can rely on them.
When the time comes...
I think he is the kind of person I would want to talk to in such a situation.
Thank you very much.
Well then, let's see how well you two get along.
Yes, ma'am.
Angelem released a new single "Red Line Life is Beautiful" last December 13th.
Yes, sir.
Red Line is a very cool song.
You can see Angelem's cool or cool-headedness in the song, and I hope you'll pay attention to it.
I hope you'll pay attention to it.
I think those two songs are really cool.
They're very bright and pop songs.
The song starts with two new members, Mikiko Shimoita and Hana Goto.
Yes.
I felt like that was the beginning of the new formation of Angeleum.
I think I like it because it gives a sense of a bright future.
Yes, and did I interrupt you?
Ochanouma is going to release our first album "Channel 1" on January 10 next year.
Yes, sir!
This is our first album.
There are 5 new songs in it.
and the first unit song of Ocha-no-Uma.
There are a lot of songs on this album.
This album is packed with all the charm of Ochano-Uma so far.
We hope many people will listen to it!
Please take a look at the video below!
Please take a look!
Music
Thank you for watching!
Finally, the first day of the event is about to begin.
We've come this far in a bit of a flurry,
I'm pretty nervous,
I didn't have time to let my mind rest.
But I only have one chance to come here, so I'm going to make the most of it.
I will be at the Kaha Marina,
I'm going to give it my all.
Let's do our best.
Let's see everyone, even those in the back.
I think they are looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Now.
When I joined, I didn't expect it,
I didn't think I would be on such a big stage within a year,
I'm nervous.
I don't know if it's because it's only the 28th,
I don't know if it's because it's only the 28th, but I don't really feel the actual coolness of the event.
I'm just nervous like I was at the concert in Yoyogi.
Yes, 1, 2, last.
Yes, one, two,
OK!
Thank you very much.
Xingfeng, Xingfeng.
Xinhong, Xinhong.
Great.
Want to gather around, Fuku-chan?
Oh!
I'm in.
I can't deliver it, I can't deliver it.
Hang on, hang on, hang on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
All right.
Somebody, somebody tell him.
I don't know what to do.
Okay, okay. Here we go.
Yes, sir.
Well, Genki is going on stage at Yokohama Arena for the first time in 9 years.
What is it?
I will do my best to shine.
I will do my best.
Yes, I will.
I'll be dancing like I'm nervous.
Ponky ponky ponky ponky discoing
We are one
Yes, we are alive The Ningandas
Yes, yes, yes, The Ningandas
Come on with me
Bum Bum Bum...
Bump it up
Oh Yeah Yeah Yeah...
We are alive!
Because we are troubled
The Ningen
Yeah Yeah Yeah The Ningen
Idol Limon
Calcon
Djambo Gajambo
Rin Nemi
Oh Yeah!
When I was born in this world
I'm already Let's Red!
Dance Dance Dance Dance
Do jambo, gajambo
Rinnemi
Do jambo, jambo, jambo
Rin Nemi
10-years after the first represents thedynday
10-years 17-years
10-years Oh Oh
Dorion, the new A beautiful star
Dorion, laugh A beautiful star
Dorion DORION STAR
I want to be happy I want to protect you
I'm sure you'll understand my true feelings
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
WE ARE L.I.C.E
Hohohoho
Hey Go Go Go
I want to be happy
I want to protect you
Everybody
I know I can do it
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
I want to make you happy
I want to wrap you in my love
No matter how old I get
Wow! It's youth
Go, go, go, go, go!
We are alive
You're young, you're young, my beautiful star
You're young, oh, hot, my beautiful star
You're young, hey, what, oh
Beautiful Star
Santa Claus won't come if you don't go to bed early
Shion Tanaka of Angelum and
and Nanami Kubota of Ochanoma.
We'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
So let's not think too much and answer at a quick pace.
Yes, I'm Nanami Kubota.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Only 11 days left in 2023.
What's the perfect word for you this year?
I found my goal.
What was the most impressive scene at a show you attended this year?
The concert in Okayama Prefecture.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you hear the words "reward yourself"?
Chocolate.
What is the key point of today's makeup?
Orange makeup.
This year was the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.
Looking back on the past year, what was the most historic moment for you?
The Hello Project 25th anniversary concert.
Singing many songs
I was able to see the OGs perform.
I see.
There were many things that caught my attention.
Then...
What was the most impressive performance you attended this year?
Okayama?
Yes, that's right.
We had a lot of gigs this year.
But the most impressive scene was...
One of my dreams came true at a concert in Okayama Prefecture.
A dream?
Yes, I did.
Ever since I was a trainee, I wanted to sing with Masaki Sato.
I had a goal to be on stage with him.
That dream came true for the first time in Okayama Prefecture.
I see. So that's how it was.
I sang next to him and our eyes met a lot.
I will never forget this scene.
I've watched the video a hundred times.
I was smiling.
That's nice.
I see, so you have such memories.
Yes.
So the key to today's makeup was orange?
Yes, that's right.
I told you earlier that I was a bit hesitant.
I used to wear pink makeup.
I wanted to try orange makeup.
I tried orange makeup the other day.
I tried orange makeup the other day, and I felt it blended in better than pink.
I'd like to try a wider variety of makeup colors from now on.
Orange makeup looks good on you.
Thank you very much.
We'll take your questions after the VTR.
Halostei
Angsturm Red Line Nauwonsaayon
Angsturm, Life is Beautiful.
Haloste
Next, I'd like to ask Shion-chan a question.
Yes, I will do my best.
Yes, I will try my best
If you could get a present from Santa Claus for Christmas soon, what would you expect?
A year's supply of sweets
What is the thing you put the most energy into for the year 2023?
Music video
Angulum has become 11 members with the addition of a new member.
What is your role in Angulum now?
Door ballet
If you were to write one kanji character to describe the year 2023, what would it be?
Back
Hello Project's 25th anniversary
What is the essence of Hello Project that you have newly discovered in the past year?
Rhythm
Thank you very much.
I'm curious about a lot of things.
Let's see...
If you were to write one kanji character for the year 2023, would it be "back"?
Yes, back.
That was the last year of my teenage years.
The year 2023...
That's why it's the last one.
If you express it in kanji, it's the last.
So I thought it didn't sound right if it was the last.
In the back of the back.
back
I chose "back".
I see.
What is the other thing that Shion Chou has devoted the most energy to in 2023?
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
Well, there was the addition of a new member.
And Akari Takeuchi's graduation.
There were a lot of single releases like that.
I wanted to make it more memorable.
I wanted to make the music videos more memorable and memorable.
We put a lot of energy into each music video.
I put a lot of energy into each music video.
I want you to see this.
Ansuruno's music video
I can feel how much fun you guys are having!
I love it so much.
Thank you very much.
Halo! Stay tuned for more after this!
This is Natsuyaki Miyabi.
I'm Yume from Chuchu Snacks.
I will do my best to make something delicious.
Let's do our best!
Sir, what would you like to make today? Yes, Mr. Kudo is an octopus! So, octopus pasta.
Fishing style. Oh, that's good! I'm so happy! I'm looking forward to the seasonality of this dish.
This time, fish. Well, octopus is not really a fish, but I've been asked to join in on the seafood side of things,
I want to eat a lot of fish, and I want to cook a lot of fish. Yes, I will do my best. I will do my best.
This one is, ah, nyah.
What was smooth before has become a little heavier. It's a little heavier. It's a thick sauce.
Now, what would you like to start with this time? Yes, I would like to cut the ingredients for the pasta.
Please do.
I don't really know what it is about octopus, because I don't hear many people talking about octopus. Collecting collectibles?
Like collecting goods, going to aquariums, buying octopus when you see it.
You buy octopus for food? Yes! I buy, eat, watch, and collect octopuses.
I am very active in octopus life. What is octopus life? Tell us about tako-katsu.
Taco katsudo means octopus goods in the house, figurines, figurines, or guide dolls?
Oh!
We also have a book called "Textbook of Octopus" to study the ecology of octopuses.
Yes!
That's amazing! So there is such a thing.
Yes, they do.
Is this your way of cutting, Mr. Kuroki?
Yes! I learned it from him. I made tako-meshi (octopus rice), and this is how I did it.
I didn't do this too often, but I turned it this way. I thought it was very good.
Oh, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
You're good at it.
You're good at it. I think I've already cut octopus well.
I've already cut octopus.
The color is very festive for Christmas. It's cut and beautiful.
I was thinking about making this a star on top of that freebie. If I make it a little bigger, I can fine-tune it.
I'll use a little bit of a full mold. Like a happy star.
Yes, that's right. Like a little wow. It's nice, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Did you get it? You did it once.
I did it once.
How is it? Let me see. What is it?
Isn't it good?
What's good? Oh, it's a happy star. It's a happy, happy planet.
It's like a crowd.
There are octopus crowds.
What's that?
It's a family of people out. A happy star has been formed.
That's what I imagined.
Yes, I did.
I want it.
Next, I'll boil the noodles, and then it's almost done.
The time has come.
There are 4.5 liters.
So 45 grams.
It goes in pretty well.
Have you done it before?
Everyone has done it successfully.
Don't put so much pressure on me.
Everyone has done it.
Do you want me to just poof with this?
I'll be fine.
I'll do it.
Yes, I'm sure.
It'll be fine. I might say something funny. I'm sorry. I put too much pressure on you, for sure.
On Tako-chan. It's okay. I'll be fine. Just break it up a little. Let's mix it in.
I'm boiling the pasta, and while it's boiling, I'm going to put the broccoli in the pot with the pasta.
Yes, I'll add the broccoli to the pasta. The broccoli will be cooked for about 1 minute. It's small.
So we do it together. All together. The flavor of the vegetables is also added to the broccoli.
Now, let's get to the point. Yes, okay. Yes, please say it. We only have 10 seconds left. Here's a point of discussion.
The boiled broccoli should be cooled in cold water. Cool. Yes, sir. Yes. Yes, yes. Five seconds to go. Why don't we start with this cold one?
Okay, let's start with the broccoli. Okay, just the broccoli. Absorb it. Let's cool it down.
Thank you very much. Okay. Yes, that's OK.
By doing so, this color will be very vivid. Wow, it's really beautiful. Yes. It will be beautiful. Yes.
Do you see how the water is a little muddy? Oh, it's true. Yes, yes. It was so clear. Yes. Thank you very much. Here you go. Bon appétit.
Hmm! It's time. Yes, it's delicious! Taste. Yes, it has saltiness, doesn't it? It has a salty taste.
How's it taste? How is it? Hardness? It's a little bit hard. A little hard? It's a little hard. Do you want me to wait a bit?
No, I like one eye. Oh, okay, then. This one. I like octopus. I like noodles that are chewy. Firm. I'll take care of this, Sensei. Dangerous.
No, it's delicious. Oh! Oh, there. I forgot something important.
Ah.
Save the pasta cooking water. Save it, it's important.
It's just a little bit, if you save it.
I'll just leave it like that.
And since it's sticking to the pasta, you can pour this over the pasta.
Oh, I see.
I'll leave it here for a while.
So the boiling water is also a seasoning?
It is a very important seasoning.
When I made tako meshi, I added it afterwards.
I also put it in after.
Did you put it in first?
I think we put it in first.
Some for flavor, some for decoration.
The texture also changes.
Some are soft, some are hard.
And at the end...
Wow!
Here it comes again.
Put the meat in.
Add the meat oil
Emulsify the water and emulsify the water and emulsify the water and emulsify the oil that was there earlier
Water and oil.
It's okay, isn't it?
Yes, I'm fine.
Now we're ready.
I'm going to make it more exciting.
Curly pasta.
Curly.
Like this?
Yeah, and then you hold it right here.
One?
That's right.
And this one here.
I'll pinch it for you when I pull it out.
I'll pinch it for you.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just make sure you get it on top of the two piles so it doesn't fall apart.
That looks hard.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's going to be fine.
Okay, okay, okay.
The box is on fire after all!
It's so juicy and delicious.
Like this.
Let's start with the broccoli.
Stick it in.
Don't let it fall apart.
It's good. It's good.
It's good.
I'll stab it.
Looks good.
I got it.
Is that a star?
It's a little more buried.
It's got a little bit of leg buried in it.
Just a little?
I can't or I wouldn't be able to stand up.
It's like wearing a crown.
And finally...
More snow.
Let's get some more snow on the ground.
Here we go.
Cute. Wow.
Snow. It's so cute.
Look at you, you're so cute.
I think it's good.
It's done!
Yay!
Thank you.
Now, that's it, Tako's Tako Pasta is ready.
It is completed.
Thank you very much.
How do you like it? Try making it.
Yes, I think so. I was very happy that we were able to make such a lovely dish together during the Christmas season.
There were many new challenges, like chopping bell peppers.
So I'm really looking forward to eating it.
We are also a little bit excited.
Yes, it was like this.
Please enjoy the food as soon as possible.
Yes, I'll eat it.
Mmmm...
Well, what do you think?
It's delicious.
That's good.
I carefully balanced the sweetness and saltiness,
The octopus is very firm, so the texture is very enjoyable,
The pasta was just the right consistency for me, as I like my pasta firm.
It was also good. It was amazing, I could hear the crunch and the sound of the octopus while I was eating it,
Oh no, it was amazingly good.
There is an amazing aftertaste of burnt onions.
Amazing. That was good. You are an outer star worker, aren't you?
Yes.
I would love to see you on Hello Kitchen again.
I would like to remind you that every month from the 3rd to the 7th is Fish Day,
I hope everyone will be aware of this and put fish on the table,
I hope that everyone will be aware of this and put fish on the table and eat fish together. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Yes, please do.
So, please come to Hello Kitchen again to taste our delicious food,
Please come to Hello Kitchen again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your time.
Good-bye.
Bye~.
That looked delicious.
Looked delicious.
I'm starving.
In the VTR, Yumi Kudo was talking about Fish Day.
Actually, I'm a member of the fish day support group.
Thank you very much!
Every month from the 3rd to the 7th is Fish Day.
If I eat fish or something between the 3rd and 7th of each month
I try to post it on my blog when I eat fish or something on the 3rd to 7th of every month.
I made chawanmushi (steamed egg custard) with shrimps at home the other day.
It had a lot of shrimp in it and was very tasty.
I hope you will eat fish, shrimp, octopus, etc. for the next 3 to 7 days.
I would be very happy if you could eat shrimp and octopus as well as fish from the 3rd to the 7th.
In the VTR, you talked about cooking with Christmas in mind.
It's almost Christmas.
I had a Christmas party with one of our members, Ms. Omoe Kamikuni.
We had a Christmas party.
We did that.
We did.
It was wonderful!
Rio Kamiguni loves Christmas.
She said she was going to have a lot of Christmas parties before Christmas.
I said, "Let's do it first.
I said, "Let's do it," and she invited me.
We bought chamomileys and pizzas.
We had a Christmas party.
It was a small one, but we did it.
That's a dream come true.
He was the senior of your dreams, wasn't he?
Having a Christmas party together... that's wonderful.
Thank you very much.
Hallo! Ste.
This is Shion Tamenaga from Angulum and Nanami Kubota from Ocha no Ma.
Nanami Kubota of Ochanomaha, and I'll be back soon with a new episode of "Halo! STE!
As I mentioned in the opening.
As I mentioned in the opening, we are both trainee members of Halo! Pro trainees, so we must have a lot of memories in common.
Pro trainees, we must have a lot of memories in common.
We wrote down our most memorable memories in each other's sketchbooks.
We wrote them down in our sketchbooks.
I'd like to announce it now!
When I heard this, I thought
When I heard this, I thought, "This is the only way.
I couldn't think of anything else.
You're kidding, right?
No way!
It fits.
You think so?
Let's do it.
Ready?
Yes!
Oh, my God!
What? What? What?
What is that?
Wait.
What? That?
Then I want to hear it.
Yes, I'm Nanami Kubota.
I'm calling at night.
When we started as trainees.
ZEPP Nagoya and ZEPP Number.
We had live shows.
When there were two days in a row
we would stay in a hotel room by ourselves
Sometimes we stayed in a hotel by ourselves.
Yes, I did.
And every time I called
I would call Kazuo Tamura
We talked a lot about how we reflected on the day together
and talked about the future together.
At that time, I was still
I was still in junior high school and he was a year older than me.
I was a junior high school student and he was my senior.
I saw her as a kind of big sister to me.
Yeah, yeah.
So I felt really safe.
Thanks to that phone call.
I felt like I could do my best tomorrow.
That's right.
I was thinking that this was the only way for me.
I see.
I remember...
I remember, but...
I didn't think it would be there.
Well, I...
We went to the amusement park together.
I think I remember that.
The first time? It was about the first time.
First time.
We went to the amusement park.
We went to an amusement park.
It was at an amusement park.
I had never been to an amusement park with a friend before.
I've never been to an amusement park with friends.
It was just us.
I mean, my mom and her friends were there, but...
but it was rare for me to go with friends by myself.
I've never been to an amusement park by myself with my friends.
So going to the amusement park with Nanami
I remember going to the amusement park with Nanami.
I don't know what to call it.
We talked a lot about how we wanted to make our debut
I remember we talked a lot about how we wanted to make our debut and waited for the waiting time.
It's true that both have their own memories.
They're both equally important.
Yes, they are.
I'm glad.
I didn't do the same thing.
But I'm glad we had so many memories.
I'm glad.
Yes, I do.
No, I don't.
You're here. The world is waiting for you.
Go strong. Go through them.
You're in. Everybody's looking forward to it.
Now, now, now, now It's Time to paint the future of the moon
Now, now, now It's Time
Do it for the stars
I know I can do it, I know I can do it, I know I can do it, I know I can do it, I know I can do it
The world is waiting for you
Go on strong, go on strong, go on strong
The next appearance Everybody's looking forward to it
The next appearance, the next future, paint it on
Now, now, now It's time
To wait for the stars
Now, now, now Now, now
Akiko Morimoto
Always stay positive and don't forget to laugh
Go for it, Zico!
Everyone starts out as a figurehead
But there's no time to be timid
I was scared of failing
I'm ready to take on anything
Be the non-toxic one.
You'll never be replaced by someone who'll run away from you
Don't be shy, come on, get out of your cave, wow, wow
You're here. The worlds are intersecting.
You've got to be strong. Go through it.
You're here. I hate everyone.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Paint it all over
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Nan Nan Nan Nan
Happy smile present from me!
Shio Tanaka of Angelem and Nami Kubota of Ocha-no-Ma!
Nami Kubota of Ocha no Ma presents Halo! Sta.
It's time to say goodbye!
Here's an announcement!
On December 30th and 31st
Project Year End Party 2023 Project Year End Party 2023
Goodbye & Hello will be held on December 30 and December 31!
December 31st will be held in Tokyo and Osaka at the same time!
Both Angulum and Ochanoma will perform in Osaka!
This will be our last concert of the year
We hope to see you all there!
From January 2 next year, we will be performing at the Halo! Project 2024
Winter 3 of US will start!
We will be performing as Team B.
We will be performing as Team B!
It will be the first time for Tea Horse to tour together with Angulum and Juice Juice.
This is the first time for both Angulum and Juice Juice to perform at a concert together.
This is our first time!
I hope we can learn and grow a lot
I hope we can learn and grow.
Yes, I hope so.
Angulum's new singles
Red Line, Life is Beautiful, is now on sale!
It's a beautiful song, too.
Please check out the music video!
And on January 10, we will be releasing our first album, Channel 1.
We will be releasing our first album, Channel 1, on January 10.
As this is our first album
We hope many people will listen to it!
And on January 17th, we are going to hold Angulum Concert 2023
Club Akari Takeuchi Final Live
DVD and Blu-ray of "From Angulum with love" will be released!
Yes, this live is very beautiful and I hope you will enjoy it.
Please pick up a copy!
And Ocha-no-Ma will be performing at Cho-Idol Fest tomorrow, December 21, together with Juice Juice!
We will be performing at the Cho-Idol Fest tomorrow, December 21, together with Juice Juice!
Yes, we will do our best tomorrow as well!
Good luck!
Hello! Project is a channel where the members of Halo! Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel.
Project members, so please check it out! Ste is a channel where members of the Halo! Project members will appear on this channel, so please check it out!
Project members will appear more and more on this channel, so please check it out! Ste is a channel where members of the Halo! Project members will appear on this channel more and more often, so please subscribe to the channel!
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time I'll be talking with Shion Tamenaga from Angulum and Nanami Kubota from Ocha no Ma.
Project and Nanami Kubota from Ochanoma.
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!